大家好，欢迎观看本次视频教程。
Hello everyone, welcome to this video tutorial.
今天我们将学习Python编程。
Today we will learn about Python programming.
Python是一种强大且易于学习的编程语言。
Python is a powerful and easy to learn programming language.
它具有高效的高级数据结构，并且对面向对象编程有简单的处理方式。
It has efficient high-level data structures and a simple approach to object-oriented programming.
让我们从基础开始。首先，我们需要安装Python。
Let's start with the basics. First, we need to install Python.
您可以从官方网站python.org下载。
You can download it from the official website python.org.
安装后，您可以从命令行运行Python。
After installation, you can run Python from the command line.
现在让我们编写第一个程序：打印‘你好，世界’。
Now let's write our first program: print hello world.
语法非常简单：只需键入print和引号中的字符串。
The syntax is very simple: just type print and the string in quotes.
今天的课就到这里。下次见！
That's it for today's lesson. See you next time!